

Contacts



Slupsk, Poland, 76-200



+38 097 994-75-27 48 886-844-325



salge.cos@gmail.com



<u>LinkedIn</u>



<u>GitHub</u>



<u>GoogleCloud</u>



<u>Telegram</u>

Tech Skills

- JavaScript / TypeScript / Node.js
- HTML5 / CSS
- Git / GitHub
- React
- Express
- Docker
- MongoBD/PostgreSQL
- Webpack / Parcel / Vite
- Linux / Windows servers
- Agile / Scrum

Soft Skills

- Teamwork
- Critical thinking
- Problem solving
- Creativity
- High analytics skills

Languages

- English (Intermediate)
- Ukrainian (Native)
- Poland (Basic)
- Russian (Fluent)

Certifications

Go IT school - Full Stack JS



Basics of Web UI Development

Git for distributed development



Fundamentals of software testing



Google Cloud Tech Specialist



Cryptoliteracy and blockchain

Full stack JavaScript Developer

Hennadii Samofal

I want to be part of a team in which I could develop and learn new technological stack. Switch to JS after more, then 10 years 1C development. I have good developer skills and motivations.

I worked as System Administrator, Business analytics, DataBase programmer, Support Engineer and other technical specialist. I was setting up the different equipments, programs, servers and services.

Projects

1. This is first team project on course HTML+CSS. Landing site for restaurant. A website with a responsive layout. Role: Team Lead, developer Build project on github, check for build errors and live page performance.

Restaurant MIMIHO

[HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Vite]

2. Pet-project on addition course JavaScript. Simple task for any information about banks. Role: Team Lead, developer [HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Parcel]

Mortgage - bank info

3. Siple application on JavaScript for generations any combinations world. The application is

- used in Crytoindustry, a volunteer project CoDeGenerator [HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Parcel] 4. Create the front-end part of the application for searching and viewing images by keyword
- GolT-js-hw-11 [HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Parcel] 5. Work with Telegram bot API. Add any functions: menu, answers, mini game, send and
- receive any format data, work with any keyboards. Telegram Bot - Node.js [Telegram-bot-api, Express, PostgreSQL, sequelize]
- 6. Front-end written on React + TypeScript + Axios + Mobx. Back-end written on Express work with MongoDB, jwt-tokens, email-autorotation request.

Work Experience

DataBase Programmer TOV Group Veneto

April 2015 - up to now | Ukraine

- Microsoft SQL servers 2008-2019 (setup, configuration, backUP, management)
- Microsoft Windows 2012-2022 server (setup, configuration, administration) -Active Directory, RDP, RemoteApp, FTP
- Ubuntu Linux server (Web-server, Mail-server, NAT, NAS, VPN, firewall, DHCP, cron)
- MikroTik (RouterOS) CAPsMAN, NAT, firewall, port-forwarding, VPN, WireGuard
- <u>Nagios</u> provides monitoring of all mission-critical infrastructure components including applications, services, operating systems, network protocols, systems metrics, and network infrastructure.
- Cloud GoogleCloud, MS Azure, Amazon AWS (Vm, networks, config for bissnes)
- Thinstation thinclient PXE boot from network
- Entware, Optware, embedded linux systems
- Special service in Cloud for data exchange between Android-mobile and 1C Enterprise (exchange HTTP\JSON) Back-end: "datacollector-webservice" on Python Front-end: Android-mobile and 1C Enterprise
- I worked with various data formats: XML, XLS, DBF, CSV, JSON, EDI.
- I worked with various API: WebCheck, SmartKassa, PrivatBank, TascomBank and e.t.c
- I worked with various equipment: BarCode or QR scanners, scales, kassa, banking terms, receipt printer
- The main activity was related to accounting and programs integrated with 1C Enterprise, M.E.DOC. and company web-site.
- ▶ 1C 8.3 / 1C 7.7 Enterprise

DataBase Programmer Gurt-baby

August 2013 - April 2015 | Ukraine

- Microsoft Windows 2012 R2 server (setup, configuration, administration) -Active Directory, RDP, RemoteApp, DHCP, FTP
- Site company on Joomla CMS
 - add new sale promotion, price, currency converter.
 - add <u>LiqPay</u> ukrainian payment system.
 - add <u>Jivochat</u> ukrainian payment system.
- Network devices, Video surveillance system (setup, configuration, administration)
- ▶ 1C 8.2 / 1C 7.7 Enterprise

DataBase Programmer TD MANN

January 2012 - August 2013 | Ukraine

- Microsoft Windows 2003 R2 server (setup, configuration, administration) -Active Directory, RDP, DHCP, FTP
- <u>Ubuntu Linux server</u> (Web-server, Mail-server, NAT, NAS, VPN, firewall, cron)
- Nagios provides monitoring of all mission-critical infrastructure components including applications, services, operating
- ▶ 1C 8.2 / 1C 7.7 Enterprise

System administrator TOV Dniproinvest-ch

April 2005 - January 2012 | Ukraine

• Microsoft Windows 2003 R2 server (setup, configuration, administration) -Active Directory, DHCP, RDP, FTP, Mail-server

• Panasonic KX-TDA100 Hybrid IP-PBX System and SIP is Internet telephony

- Network devices, Video surveillance system (setup, configuration, administration)
- 1C 7.7 Accounting for Ukraine (setup, update, administration)

Education

CHERKASY STATE TECHNOLOGICAL UNIVERSITY Ukraine

September 2002 - June 2007 | System programming

Bachelor's degree

CHERKASY EAST EUROPEAN UNIVERSITY Ukraine

September 2007 - June 2008 | Economic Cybernetics

Master's degree